I live in Lone Light.
I barely escaped because glint hawks attack anyone who ventures out.
We have so few shots.
Will you help?
We have nowhere else to turn.
Sometimes members receive an honorarium for the hunt.
A C should have accepted this one, but he refused.
The price was too low.
How generous in the past, I would have gone with talk is to handle this.
What say you and I take it on?
I'll meet you at Lone Light.
What about Red?
Ma?
Are you in or not?
All right.
I'll meet you there as soon as I can
start.
Good.
Yeah.
It'll keep my stomach quite.
No.
By the sun.
Are you Nora?
I've never seen what a hunting grounds before Or the Hunter's lodge.
How interesting.
Who are you?
Where are you?
Here.
Well, my Ma hunter, of course.
And a member of the hunters launch.
But I don't mind being out here.
At least no one complains about my clothes or my manners or my personality.
Don't let him in.
He'll drive people off with its incessant chattering.
Or he's thinks of fish again, That sort of thing.
I don't stink of fish.
Do I?
No, it's more like What for?
Well, that's something.
What do you do here?
The trials here focus on the most important part of hunting.
Keeping your stamina up haunting isn't a sprint.
It's a gauntlet.
So all you offer his training.
What trial will you run today?
The remains of watchers rest on free rises.
Loot all of them before time runs out and you pass.
It Sounds simple, but watch out for all the other machines down there.
Start timing once you slide down the road.
Wait.
Yeah.
Here we go again.
You want a blazing sun on your first attempt?
Congratulations
for this trial.
You'll need to be ableto tie down a trampler and shoot off component, but you'll need the right weapon first.
In this trial, you must tie down a trampler and shoot off the component under its belly.
All start timing once you choose a role.
Come here.
Tramp alert.
Weakness to freeze.
Strong against fire excavation horns.
Destroying these components disables the excavation horn attacks power cell processing unit.
Destroying this component disables the fire based attacks and triggers an explosion.
You want a blazing sun on your first attempt?
Congratulations.
Now's your chance to show you can snare Glynn talks were them close to you then tie them down in time to pass this test.
Are you ready?
Spotted?
Oh,
you want a blazing sun on her first attempt?
Congratulations.
I should leave for now till the next hunt.
About time You showed up with more Klain Hawks Incoming!
No
more coming.
You're not walking away from this.
No more time to recover.
No
go!
That seems to have taken care of them.
But more always come The soldiers at mornings watch Don't even bother to fight them anymore.
It seems like they're coming from upriver.
I could track them back to the source.
But if more come here, I'll watch the village.
You go ahead.
I thought you wanted to do this together.
You don't need me to hold your hand.
Hardens on this flower are so strange.
Before that,
I just got a tough storey
working talks
You're not gonna like this
There
go
their snot Ma carcasses everywhere.
No wonder they want talks were drawn here
Blinds us Amateurs believe easy tracks to follow
you You, You You
No
baby
Wait!
These must be the snap.
More hunters
I'm here on behalf of the nearby village.
Seems your kill zone is creating a Glynn talk problem for them.
Yeah, well, they're not the only people with problems.
If we don't get enough snap mall hearts to pay off alone, we lose everything I don't follow.
I borrowed shards to buy seeds.
The harvest went bust, and now they're coming for the dead.
We could lose the farm, our home.
I'm sorry about that.
But Glen, talks are attacking people because of what you're doing here.
Not my problem.
None of us are leaving until I get what I came for.
None of us.
You didn't think it was just us two, did you?
I'll make it simple for you.
Stop slaughtering machines for one components, leaving the rest to waste.
Now I'll make it simple for you.
That's not going to happen.
So get out of here.
It seems we've come to an impasse.
Make your move.
So be it.
No.
Enjoy your last.
Yeah,
a lawyer.
Fools bit off more than they could chew.
What a waste.
But now I know you can handle yourself.
You are watching The whole time.
Of course.
Carcass made the sunlight is passing taught me many things.
First of which wass ah hawk never abandons their thrush.
Wait, Are you saying I'd like to sponsor you for membership?
What do you say to hunting machines, winning trophies and unseating a cease?
I'm in.
I'll meet you back at the largest in his I'm able.
You mean you?
Yeah.
I can always use these.
Teo,
wait.
Really, really, really
Hardens on this flower are so strange.
Metal flower code fragment downloaded function true Desta Many crumbled city settles over us like a forgetful does.
But we're older than those cities We began as a mineral way emerged into plant life and into the animal state and then into being human And always we have forgotten our former states Except in early spring, when we slightly recall being green again
Myths of the old ones Any card you devout knows that the truth of the old ones is laid out plainly In the articles of the sun Faith A twilight time came upon them as is the cycle of things followed by a long night and finally our ancestors birth in the new dawn.
Since that Don Carty, history has been written in the path of the sun, not the faded glories of those who came so long before us.
Even the leaves of the old ones found by Arman are long since cracked and fallen to death.
Nevertheless, collected here for study are the colourful beliefs of the old ones held by other tribes, which may offer a small insight into those tribes.
Primitive views of the world.
The ulcer I am, as might be expected of you.
The workings of the world is a device one where all things behave according to mechanical rigidity and not the sun's divine rhythms, the movement of the tribes of the seasons, even the stars at night.
All are accounted for by this interlocking and complicated mechanism.
The old ones were the caretakers of this great machine, but they neglected their duty to maintain it.
The world machine thus fell into disrepair, and the civilisation of the old ones collapsed with it.
Now the OSCE, Aram used their myth to be raped the other tribes as negligent and a hammer upon their own importance.
How convenient that they're tinkers and metal workers alone might learn this mechanism secrets and improve upon it with their ingenuity and even more fanciful tale of censure comes from the Nora barbarians.
They believe that the old ones turned away from the teachings of the North female God Theo mother and eloped with the machines to build their mighty cities.
Having failed to tempt the nor to join them, the machine's rallied under a great metal devil and attacked the all mother interventions.
She stripped the machines of their wisdom, reducing them to the simple metal beasts we see today without the assistance of the machines.
The old ones were left to wander as exiles never permitted to return to the isolation of the Nora and their strange feminine rights from the survivors of this so called punishment grew the other tribes.
And this is why the North Show distrust to all outside their borders for were descended from the faithless and do not shun the trappings of the ancient world.
Surprisingly, it is the bannock whose belief is most similar to our own.
Though their mythology is bizarre in many other ways, they believe the old ones grew complacent, thinking there was no challenge they could not overcome and in their pride were undone.
Hence, the minute give them no more attention than any other tribe defeated by the harshness of the land.
In fact, many pinoke Hunter's point to the absence of ruins in Bandar is a sign that the old ones were never strong enough to endure its challenges.
They claim that only the machines and the eunuch have ever roamed there, and so they have nothing to learn from the ancients.
The distant to target, however, believe that the old ones are still with them at all times.
In new Target ritual, those who die are returned to the soil, nourishing the land and living on through new growth.
As long as the dead are remembered, they will contribute to the harvests and make them bountiful plutocracy the richness of their territory.
Plainsong is evidence of this unique and disturbing cycle.
Finally, as they're a few living scholars of the tenor way, regrettably denied any insight from that tribe from what is known, though it seems they have little concept of a wider history at all.
But of course, this is what elevates a scholar of Meridian from a bloodthirsty raider to be aware of all the sun's light touches.
However strange and unlikely details
a Guide to Ban, Nor in the Eunuch, by the well travelled
The sun shines golden on these times where one can experience the whole world without leaving.
The streets of Meridian for the gates are thrown open and the world comes to us.
And yet, as I walked among the markets, I heard a question on the air again.
What to make of the boy, Nuck?
Thie, stoic, silent northern hunters, thes men and women of the ice.
Unfortunately for my investigations, the nuke outlanders seldom remain in Meridian long enough for exhaustive study.
It is believed there cold blood does not take well to the heat.
If I was to seek this knowledge, I would have to undergo the ordeal of taking up travel pack and quill and journeying to their homeland.
And so it came to be that I spend a miserable time living among the mannequin frigid banner.
The duck speak of their territory in reverent tones, but plainly it is the most uncomfortable place in the world.
There is beauty, soaring glaciers of jewel fuse, billows of steam that erupt from the earth, whirling auroras in the skies above.
Yes, yes, But the novelty quickly passes and the bone freezing chill remains.
It is a country of the moon, for in the day the sun is reduced to a needle's eye through the grey, and in the night the moon rises four times with.
There is no welcome not in the land nor from its people, though I lived among one of the were ex, something like a group of families, but without the civility of a noble house, each member must prove that they possess the will to survive alone.
They seek to always be challenged whether the jaws of the machine are simply in their daily existence.
I tried to explain my position that a cardio faces a challenge, devices a solution and then, with the challenge overcome, can live in contentment.
This concept horrified them.
It was made clear that when I expected to sleep, I must dig out my own hollow in the snow for my tent.
When I expected to eat, I must hunt food myself.
I hid my disappointment.
After all, I had participated in a hunting trial or two in my time and accepted.
On the third morning I was able to bring down a rabbit much like those seen in the Plains, but with a downy snow coat.
Upon presenting my prize to the weir and I received only blank stares until one indicated I must skin and prepare it.
Reader, I will spare you the details.
The experience nearly changed me to eat only maise bread forever more.
I had barely finished my gory portion before the look set off on a machine hunt with their shaman, a man with machine binding sewn into his very skin.
Perhaps another challenge.
Decency, he claimed the sense the machine spirits close by.
And sure enough, the hunters and I follow tracks in the snow to a grazer hurt.
The bannock made short work of them with their spares and struck with a curious desire to prove myself.
I threw myself into stripping a fallen machine for parts.
Instead of praise for my initiative, I was subjected to the shaman's cursing and wailing and hauled back to camp by selling Hunter.
Eventually, she explained that the machine spirits must be thanked for the gift of a successful hunt before any parts are harvested.
Truly, I was despairing of the shifting wilds have been a culture and long for the certainty of the Sun's guidance that night, mercifully, my last, my companions and another where it gathered under a pitiless clear sky to exchange songs their way of recording history.
Some understand the cliffs, but choose not to use them, asking What is a song without voices?
By this point, I knew better than to answer.
My deeds warranted a whole verse in the song of my companions, but from what I could make out, much was lost in the translation.
Still, there was laughter enough, and many promised to leave me of Anouk farewell mark for our time.
Together, I parted ways with the way wreck not far from the high bloom, and set about climbing back down to Don Sentinel and with its sun blessed civilisation.
As for the farewell marks, I saw no such thing when I packed my Webley frozen belongings.
Another minute mystery, perhaps, And my advice to you, dear reader, is to let these people keep their mysteries to themselves.